<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Frippenator Updates</title>
<link>https://frippenator.neocities.org</link>
<ttl>10</ttl>
<description></description>
<copyright></copyright>
<lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 17:20:57 -0500</lastBuildDate>
<generator>Super Simple RSS</generator>
<webMaster>fripp@disroot.org</webMaster>
<item>
<title>Comment widget now live!</title>
<link></link>
<description>
Jesus fuck, that took forever. My IDE randomly stopped syncing correctly and I had to push it to GitHub several times before hard resetting Codium for the widget to work. Actual hell on earth. &quot;Share and enjoy,&quot; à la the Sirius Cybernetics Corporation.
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 22 August 2025 17:17:27 -0500</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>New blog entry + rearranged some things</title>
<link>blog/2025_08_21.html</link>
<description>
I remembered that I can just make seperate HTML files for each entry rather than make one gigantic blog file. I think I&apos;ll just stick to that. Expect a guestbook or some sort of comment widget soon, and perhaps an archive of my first layout whenever I figure out how I want to showcase it.
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 21 August 2025 17:26:15 -0500</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Blog section is up!</title>
<link>blog.html</link>
<description>
Now to figure out how to add tags and make it not clunky... If anyone knows how to make static blogging pages a bit more convenient, do share. I might just bite the bullet and just post stuff on an external site, but where&apos;s the fun in that?
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 20 August 2025 17:55:21 -0500</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Things look different around here...</title>
<link></link>
<description>
Wow! It&apos;s so empty and generic! I decided to give my site a huge overhaul after a year of not updating it. It was far too daunting when it was all fancy-like... It&apos;ll start having more character eventually, but I needed a blank slate. Mind the mess.
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 18 August 2025 14:17:18 -0500</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>RSS feed now up</title>
<link></link>
<description>
Finally added an RSS feed to this site, rather than an ever-expanding wall of text for updates. Was rather clunky. This is a test... cheers to making websites and whatnot.
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 7 August 2025 08:45:25</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
